A Guide to the Blanchette H. Rockefeller Papers FA107
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1933-1994; 53/3; 16 Cubic Feet 40 Boxes
  - Women's Forum, 1979-1989 (Box 52, Folder 404)
  - Young Women's Christian Association - National Board, 1934-1943 (Box 52, Folder 405)
- Museum of Modern Art Files, 1951-1992; 53/4; 9 Cubic Feet 16 Boxes
  Mrs. Rockefeller's significant involvement with the Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) began in 1949 when her brother-in-law, Nelson A. Rockefeller, asked her to assist with the formation of a Junior Council which he hoped would attract young, talented committee and board members to the museum. Mrs. Rockefeller served as the first chair of the Junior Council. After World War II she helped form the International Council whose members were involved in the planning and financing of international exhibitions. In 1953 she was named a trustee of MoMA and she served continuously from that year until her retirement in 1987. During that time Mrs. Rockefeller twice served as president (1959-1962, 1972-1985) and was elected chairman of the Board in 1985. During her second tenure as president, MoMA successfully undertook a fundraising campaign, substantially increased exhibit and curatorial space, and added significantly to its collection of modern and contemporary art. These files are revelatory of Mrs. Rockefeller's very active role in many aspects of the museum's operation, including fundraising. Her involvement is evident in the hand-written notes generated by her to committee chairs and to donors and potential donors in her capacity as a "lay administrator." Documented here is the major fundraising event for the museum's 50th anniversary as well as files relating to the controversial issue of selling the air rights of the museum to an outside developer.
  Related Archival Materials note
  An oral history interview done for the Archives of American Art in 1970, in which Mrs. Rockefeller discusses her association with the MoMA, can be found in the Subject Series (box 16).
  - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Sculpture Garden, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 406)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Honoring Donors, 1959-1968, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 407)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Honoring Donors, 1959-1968, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 408)
  - Architecture and Design, 1963-1989 (Box 53, Folder 409)
  - Barr, Alfred H., 1975-1987 (Box 53, Folder 410)
  - Board of Trustees - General Correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 53, Folder 411)
  - Board of Trustees - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 53, Folder 412)
  - Board of Trustees - General Correspondence (A-D), 1962-1990 (Box 53, Folder 413)
  - Board of Trustees - General Correspondence (F-M), 1962-1990 (Box 54, Folder 414)
  - Board of Trustees - General Correspondence (N-R), 1962-1990 (Box 54, Folder 415)
  - Board of Trustees - General Correspondence (S-Z), 1962-1990 (Box 54, Folder 416)
  - Board of Trustees - Paley, William S., 1972-1985 (Box 54, Folder 417)
  - Business Committee, 1979-1986 (Box 54, Folder 418)
  - Business Committee - Japanese Corporate Members, 1977-1987 (Box 54, Folder 419)
  - Chairmanship (Blanchette H. Rockefeller), 1985-1987 (Box 54, Folder 420)
  - Chronological Files (A), 1978-1990 (Box 54, Folder 421)
  - Chronological Files (B), 1978-1990 (Box 54, Folder 422)
  - Chronological Files (C), 1978-1990 (Box 55, Folder 423)
  - Chronological Files (D-E), 1978-1990 (Box 55, Folder 424)
  - Chronological Files (F-G), 1978-1990 (Box 55, Folder 425)
  - Chronological Files (H), 1978-1990 (Box 55, Folder 426)
  - Chronological Files (I-K), 1978-1990 (Box 55, Folder 427)
  - Chronological Files (L), 1978-1990 (Box 55, Folder 428)
  - Chronological Files (M), 1978-1990 (Box 55, Folder 429)
  - Chronological Files (Mc), 1978-1990 (Box 56, Folder 430)
  - Chronological Files (N-O), 1978-1990 (Box 56, Folder 431)
  - Chronological Files (P), 1978-1990 (Box 56, Folder 432)
  - Chronological Files (R), 1978-1990 (Box 56, Folder 433)
  - Chronological Files (S), 1978-1990 (Box 56, Folder 434)
  - Chronological Files (T), 1978-1990 (Box 56, Folder 435)
  - Chronological Files (U-Z), 1978-1990 (Box 56, Folder 436)
  - Congress and the Arts, 1975-1981 (Box 56, Folder 437)
  - Contemporary Arts Council, 1974-1986 (Box 56, Folder 438)
  - Director, Office of, 1972-1994 (Box 56, Folder 439)
  - Drawings Committee, 1978-1991 (Box 57, Folder 440)
  - Education Committee, 1968-1992 (Box 57, Folder 441)
  - Education Committee - International Study Center, 1960-1970 (Box 57, Folder 442)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign, 1975-1977 (Box 57, Folder 443)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign, 1978-1979 (Box 57, Folder 444)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 445)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 446)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign, 1983-1985 (Box 58, Folder 447)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Corporate/Foundation Support (A-F), 1983-1985 (Box 58, Folder 448)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Corporate/Foundation Support (G-L), 1983-1985 (Box 58, Folder 449)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Corporate/Foundation Support (M-Z), 1983-1985 (Box 58, Folder 450)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Corporate/Foundation Support - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1978-1985 (Box 58, Folder 451)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Corporate/Foundation Support - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1976-1983 (Box 58, Folder 452)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (A), 1975-1985 (Box 58, Folder 453)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (B), 1975-1985 (Box 59, Folder 454)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (C), 1975-1985 (Box 59, Folder 455)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (D-G), 1975-1985 (Box 59, Folder 456)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (H-I), 1975-1985 (Box 59, Folder 457)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (J-L), 1975-1985 (Box 59, Folder 458)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (M-O), 1975-1985 (Box 59, Folder 459)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (P-R), 1975-1985 (Box 60, Folder 460)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (S), 1975-1985 (Box 60, Folder 461)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Individual Giving (T-Z), 1975-1985 (Box 60, Folder 462)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Steering Committee - Meetings, 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 463)
  - 50th Anniversary Campaign - Steering Committee - Reception, May 22, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 464)
  - Film Committee - Correspondence, 1982-1989 (Box 60, Folder 465)
  - Film Committee - Funding - Titus Auditorium, 1976-1989 (Box 60, Folder 466)
  - Film Department - Academy Award, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 467)
  - Film Department - Benefits, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 468)
  - Film Department - Benefits, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 469)
  - Film Department - Benefits, 1984-1987 (Box 61, Folder 470)
  - Film Department - Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 61, Folder 471)
  - Film Department - Correspondence - Gish, Lillian, 1975-1989 (Box 61, Folder 472)
  - Film Department - Correspondence - Video Program, 1982-1985 (Box 61, Folder 473)
  - Film Department - Correspondence - Warner Communications, 1980-1986 (Box 61, Folder 474)
  - 40th Anniversary Campaign, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 475)
  - Funding Bequests, 1974-1991 (Box 61, Folder 476)
  - Funding Bequests - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller, 1976-1991 (Box 61, Folder 477)
  - Funding Bequests - Corporate/Foundation, 1964-1985 (Box 61, Folder 478)
  - Funding Bequests - Federal/National Endowment for the Arts, 1973-1987 (Box 62, Folder 479)
  - Funding Bequests - Helena Rubenstein Foundation, 1975-1988 (Box 62, Folder 480)
  - Funding Bequests - New York State, 1974-1989 (Box 62, Folder 481)
  - General Counsel, 1975-1992 (Box 62, Folder 482)
  - International Council Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 62, Folder 483)
  - International Council Meetings, 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 484)
  - International Council Meetings, 1984-1986 (Box 62, Folder 485)
  - International Council Meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 62, Folder 486)
  - International Council Meetings, 1990-1992 (Box 63, Folder 487)
  - International Council Meetings - Members, 1956-1991 (Box 63, Folder 488)
  - International Council Meetings - Members, 1956-1991 (Box 63, Folder 489)
  - Library, 1980-1982 (Box 63, Folder 490)
  - Membership and Development, 1972-1991 (Box 63, Folder 491)
  - Museum Tower Apartment - Closing, 1981-1987 (Box 63, Folder 492)
  - Museum Tower Apartment - Transfer to Museum, 1987-1988 (Box 63, Folder 493)
  - Nominating Committee, 1970-1981 (Box 63, Folder 494)
  - Painting and Sculpture - Committee, 1984-1991 (Box 64, Folder 495)
  - Painting and Sculpture - Correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 64, Folder 496)
  - Painting and Sculpture - Correspondence - "Guernica" (Return to Spain), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 497)
  - Painting and Sculpture - Correspondence - Picasso, Jacqueline, 1980-1986 (Box 64, Folder 498)
  - Painting and Sculpture - Correspondence - Picasso Retrospective, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 499)
  - Painting and Sculpture - Correspondence - Picasso Retrospective, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 500)
  - Photographs - Expansion Project, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 501)
  - Photography Committee, 1973-1992 (Box 64, Folder 502)
  - Presidency, 1972-1987 (Box 64, Folder 503)
  - President's Activities Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 64, Folder 504)
  - Prints and Illustrated Books, 1980-1988 (Box 65, Folder 505)
  - Public Information, 1960-1988 (Box 65, Folder 506)
  - Publications Committee, 1975-1989 (Box 65, Folder 507)
  - Publicity, 1962-1989 (Box 65, Folder 508)
  - Publicity - Re-opening, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 509)
  - Special Events, 1978-1983, 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 510)
  - Special Events, 1978-1983, 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 511)
  - Special Events - Annual Fund Receptions, 1974-1987 (Box 65, Folder 512)
  - Special Events - Annual Fund Receptions, 1974-1987 (Box 65, Folder 513)
  - Special Events - Exhibitions, 1977-1993 (Box 66, Folder 514)
  - Special Events - "Party in the Garden", 1981-1991 (Box 66, Folder 515)
  - Special Events - Reopening, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 516)
  - Special Events - Reopening, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 517)
  - Special Events Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 66, Folder 518)
  - Special Gifts Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 519)
  - Trust for Cultural Resources of the City of New York - Coordination Agreement, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 520)
  - Trust for Cultural Resources of the City of New York - Sale Agreement, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 521)
  - Trust for Cultural Resources of the City of New York - Bond Issue, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 522)
  - Trust for Cultural Resources of the City of New York - Bond Issue, 1980; 1 volume (Box 67, Folder 523)
  - Trustee Committee for Special Events, 1982-1985 (Box 67, Folder 524)
  - Trustee Committees, 1966-1990 (Box 67, Folder 525)
  - Trustee Giving, 1963-1988 (Box 67, Folder 526)
  - Transfer of Development Rights, 1979; 3 volumes (Box 68, Folder 526A)
- Political Files, 1961-1992; 53/5; 3 Cubic Feet 3 Boxes
  This series documents Mrs. Rockefeller's interest and involvement in politics through her contributions to various political causes and candidates - both Democratic and Republican.
  - General (A-B), 1964-1990 (Box 69, Folder 527)
  - General (C), 1975-1991 (Box 69, Folder 528)
  - General (D), 1982-1989 (Box 69, Folder 529)
  - General (E-H), 1970-1990 (Box 69, Folder 530)
  - General (I-L), 1965-1991 (Box 69, Folder 531)
  - General (M), 1974-1991 (Box 69, Folder 532)
  - General (N-P), 1977-1990 (Box 69, Folder 533)
  - General (R), 1961-1988 (Box 70, Folder 534)
  - General (S), 1973-1987 (Box 70, Folder 535)
  - General (T-Y), 1979-1990 (Box 70, Folder 536)
  - Contributions - Brademas, John, 1975-1982 (Box 70, Folder 537)
  - Contributions - Guidelines, 1975-1986 (Box 70, Folder 538)
  - Contributions - Javits, Jacob, 1976, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 539)
  - Contributions - Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 70, Folder 540)
  - Contributions - Yearly Tabulations, 1981-1990 (Box 70, Folder 541)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1983-1992 (Box 70, Folder 542)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 543)
  - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, 1983-1989 (Box 70, Folder 544)
  - Democrats for the 80's, 1982-1989 (Box 71, Folder 545)
  - Democrats for the 90's, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 546)
  - Forum Institute and USA Votes, 1986-1988 (Box 71, Folder 547)
  - Fundraisers - Guest Lists, 1979-1990 (Box 71, Folder 548)
  - Fundraisers - Breaux, John, 1986, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 549)
  - Fundraisers - Byrd, Robert, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 550)
  - Fundraisers - Byrd, Robert, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 551)
  - Fundraisers - Caperton, Gaston, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 552)
  - Fundraisers - Daschle, Tom, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 553)
  - Fundraisers - Dayton, Mark, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 554)
- Restricted Material, 53/6
  - Rockefeller Family (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller letters to children, 1959 Wedding invitation list (Hope's?) Genealogies Family of Abby Rockefeller Mauz Family of Nelson A. Rockefeller Family of Laurance S. Rockefeller Family of Winthrop Rockefeller Family of David Rockefeller Family of Margaret Strong de Cuevas The Cousins Meetings Fifth Generation Personal correspondence Meetings Rockefeller Family events William Rockefeller family Aldrich Family
    Restricted from scholarly access.
  - Estate of Mr. John D. Rockefeller 3rd (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Estate of Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Wills, 1982, 1984 Planning, 1983-1986 Art appraisals, 1985, 1992
  - Subject Files (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Art collection General, 1981-1992 Appriasals/Disposition, 1978-1988 Gifts to museums, 1985-1989 Lists, 1973-1991 Miscellany, 1979-1992 Christmas, 1974-1992 Lists, 1939-1946 Households Fieldwood Farm Insurance/Legal, 1978-1980, 1984-1989 Salary information, 1973-1989 Security, 1978-1988 Trust for Mutual Understanding, 1985-1992
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Director, Office of, 1972-1994 Searches for, 1969, 1972 Museum Tower apartment Art works and property appraisals, 1987 Personnel, 1964-1991
  - Financial (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Budget, comparisons, & tax info, 1933-1944 Miscellany, 1939-1946 Investments, taxes, etc., 1968-1976 Payroll, 1945-1947 Colorado Fuel & Iron Corp., 1940 Trust Fund (John D. Rockefeller 3rd), 1945 Income tax, 1940-1944, 1948 Guardian Depositors Corp., 1929-1937
  - Pocantico Hills (Box 80, Folder 1)
    Carriage Museum study, 1978 Proposed division of property, 1978 Greenrock Corporation, 1979-1993 Historic Hudson Valley Playhouse/Abeyton Lodge, Inc., 1980-1992 Rockefeller State Park Correspondence, 1978-1982, 1983-1988 Recommendations, 1979 (2 binders) Master plan, 1982
  - Staff (Box 81, Folder 1)
    Secretarial miscellany, 1945-1976 "Duties of Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller's Secretary" handbook Nurses/companions to children, 1936-1960 Dorothy Regan, 1937-1964, 1941-1974 Bertha Saunders, 1964-1984 Meg Perlman (art curator), 1982-1993
  - Rockefeller Family Office Staff (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Elizabeth McCormack/Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller Personal & confidential correspondence 1980-1987 1988-1990 Former staff, 1973-1991 Elizabeth McCormack, 1974-1991 Porter McKeever, 1978-1992 Fergus Reid, 1982-1985
- Blanchette H. Rockefeller Photographs, 1901, 1912, 1920, 1931-1932, 1937, 1940-1941, 1943-1947, 1951, 1953-1956, 1958-1962, 1964-1967, 1969-1991; 1031; 4.63 Cubic Feet 6 letter size document box, 1/2 legal size document box, 2 17"x21" oversized documet box, 18"x14" oversized document box, 15"x12" oversized document box
  This series contains photographs, negatives, a scrapbook, correspondence, and art work pertaining the the life and family of Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller.
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR) with Barbara Ferry Hooker, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR) with Barbara Ferry Hooker and Helen Huntington Hooker, Avery Fisher Hall, Philharmonic, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR) with Ivan Petrovich Pavlov, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR), Vassar College, Class of 1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR), Vassar College, Class of 1931 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR) and John D. Rockefeller 3rd (JDR 3rd), Wedding, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR) and John D. Rockefeller 3rd (JDR 3rd), Passport Photographs, 1955, 1984, 1987, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR) and John D. Rockefeller 3rd (JDR 3rd), 1956, 1964, 1966, 1971-1987, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7-10)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR) and John D. Rockefeller 3rd (JDR 3rd), 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (BHR) and John D. Rockefeller 3rd (JDR 3rd), Japan Society, 1953, 1962, 1969-1970, 1974-1975, 1978, 1981, 1985, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ferry Family, Dexter Ferry, 1954, 1981, 1983, 1986, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ferry Family, W. Hawkins Ferry, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ferry Family, 1905, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Ferry Family, Portraits (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Ferry Family, Ferry-Morse Seed Company, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ferry Family, Isaac Crippen's House (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ferry Family, Ferry Coat of Arms (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Hooker Family (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Hooker Family (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Hooker Family, Blanche Ferry Hooker, Elon H. Hooker, Barbara F. Hooker (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Hooker Family, Thomas Hooker Print (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Hooker, Helen Huntington (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Hooker Sisters (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Hooker Sisters, Barbara, Adelaide, and Helen, E. L. MacRae Painting, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Hooker Family, Coat of Arms (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Hooker Family, Hooker Electrochemical Co., Tacoma Plant, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - O'Malley Family, Cahal Hooker O'Malley, 1971, 1973, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 27-28)
  - O'Malley Family, Cormac O'Malley, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - O'Malley Family, Cormac and Family, 1987, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - O'Malley Family, Cormac and Family, 1987, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - O'Malley Family, Etain O'Malley, 1940, 1981, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - John D, Rockefeller, Sr., Lakeview Cementary, Cleveland, Ohio, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Sons, Tarrytwon Train Station, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1967,1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, The Agricultural Development Council (ADC), 1965, 1973, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Natural Institute of Social Sciences, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Princeton University (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Rockefeller Brothers (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller and Rodman Rockefeller (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Rockefeller, Mary Todhunter Clark (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Rockefeller Family, Christmas Lunches, etc., 1948 December (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Rockefeller Family, Christmas Group Portrait, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Roelofs, Helen Hooker, 1980, 1984-1986, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Roelofs, Helen, Ireland Property, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Rowntree Family, 1940-1941, 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 49-50)
  - Rowntree Family (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Group Photograph (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Child Walking (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Sun Prints (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Blanchette and John Rockefeller, Ex Libris, Print (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Album, Summer of 1930, France snd GermanyTrip (Box 3, Folder 55-56)
  - Photo Album (Box 4, Folder 57-60)
  - Asia (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Asia, India, 1954 March (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Asia, Indonesia, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Asia, Japan, Tokyo War Crimes Trial, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Asia, Japan, John Foster and Janet Dulles, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 65-66)
  - Asia, Blanchette H. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller 3rd Flying to Asia, 1951, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Asia, Japan, 1955-1956, 1960, 1964, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 69-71)
  - Asia, Japan, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Asia, Japan, Correspondence with Embassy, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Asia, Japan, Fujisankei Communications Group, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Asia, Japan, International House, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Asia, Japan, Japanese Vistors to New York City (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Asia, Japan, Japanese Chamber of Commerce and Industry of NY, Inc., First Annual Dinner, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Asia, Japan, Japanese Chamber of Commerce and Industry of NY, Inc., Second Annual Dinner, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Asia, Japan, Matsumoto Family, Miaso and Fumihiko Maki, 1952-1992, 1959, 1964, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Asia, Japan, Personal Correspondence with the Imperial Family, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Asia, Pakistan, Malaya, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Asia, Philippines, 1953, 1958, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Asia, Thailand, Royal Family, Greeting Cards, 1982; 1986; 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Asia Society, Galleries and New Building, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Daschle, Tom and Linda, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Fieldwood Farm, Horses and Barns, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Lincoln Center, Lincoln Center Theater and Performing Arts Library, Construction, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 1971, 1973-1975, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 89-91)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Architecture & Design, A Day with Frank Lloyd Wright, Ludwig Glaeser, 1978 May 4 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), International Council Meeting, 1978; 1982; 1985; 1988 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Museum Expansion Project, 1980, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Phelps Hospital, Phelps Fifth Annual Champagne Ball, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Phillip, Gifford and Joann, 35th Wedding Anniversary, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Sasakawa, Ryoichi, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Vassar College, Alumnae House (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Vassar College, Alumnae House (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Vassar College, Alumnae House, The Great Wonder, A Vision of the Apocalyse, Violet Oakley, 1924 March 24 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Hooker, Blanche Ferry, Letters of Affectionate Greetings for Her 82nd Birthday, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Hooker-Ferry Wedding, Floral Arch of Blanche Ferry Sweet Pea, 1901 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Hooker Family, Copy of Ivan Olinsky Painting (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Lincoln, Abraham (Reproduction from 1921) (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Wedding Proclamation, Violet Oakley, 1932 December 11 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Rockefeller & Andrews, Sexton Building, Superior Avenue, Cleveland, Ohio (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Hooker, Richard (1553-1600), Statue (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - O'Malley Family (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Group Photograph, School girls (Box 8)
  - Hooker Residence, "The Cottage", Greenwich, Connecticut (Box 9)
  - Hooker-Ferry Family Album (Box 10)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette Hooker, Scrapbook, 1914-1930 (Box 11)